[{'ticker': 'MSFT US', 'name': 'Microsoft Corporation develops, manufactures, licenses, sells, and supports software products. The Company offers operating system software, server application software, business and consumer applications software, software development tools, and Internet and intranet software. Microsoft also develops video game consoles and digital music.', 'target_price': 600.0, 'market_cap': 3649450.0, 'dividend_yield': 0.0072}]
